From the beginning, we hated you, but also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you, so we had to cross the wall.
Defendant Bear Lulu Yurigasaki, I ask you this.
Will you give up on love, or will you give up on kisses?
I will never give up on love, Your Honor, so I'll give up on kisses.
Growl! Please, oh please, make me a human girl!
I've just got to go to the other side of the wall. I can't let Ginkgo go alone!
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Hiroshi!
Welcome everyone this is known as the severance court the door has opened so
enter what we consider the land of enlightenment for all living things yes
even human and bare I'm the judge life sexy I'm prosecutor life cool I'm
defense counsel life beauty all right since court is not in session today I
thought I would tell you all a sexy story that might clear some of this
craziness up a bit your honor we aren't spending today looking like this are we
why not I couldn't possibly be more adorable right now problem is I'm not
feeling very cool but you look so cute cool well not as cute as me of course
order in the court
the princess who gave up on kisses she gave up on kisses let us begin the story for
that is sexy shabba da do once upon a time long before the wall of severance was
built to separate people from bears there was a lovely bear kingdom and a
lovely bear forest in that kingdom there lived a very beautiful princess she was
called Lulu for that was her name princess Lulu was heir to the throne the future Queen Lulu
princess Lulu was special from the very moment she was born in fact not a day went by without the
bears of the castle praising her vast charm and beauty how adorable you are princess Lulu you are our
kingdom's greatest treasure no pearl or gem of any sort could ever outshine your highness we are so
fortunate to serve such a smart kind and beautiful princess
we are truly blessed yes princess Lulu was by far the favorite of all the bears in all the kingdom
desire and then one day more shooting stars fell to earth than anyone had ever seen before
they were fragments of the former planet kumaria and they came from the far reaches of space
princess rejoice her majesty your mother has just given birth to a beautiful and healthy little boy
you have a baby brother now your highness that must be so exciting the king and queen are both
practically beside themselves with joy yes the long-awaited prince our beloved kingdom is finally secure
wait who's the heir the prince of course
from that day forward princess Lulu was no longer the favorite
my prince you know you're so cute oh yes how adorable you are your highness the whole kingdom is fortunate
to deserve such a kind and beautiful prince
from the very moment her brother was born the entire castle nay the entire kingdom was wild about
their new favorite the little prince princess Lulu was left alone sadly yes she became unwanted
oh my
oh hey big sis Lulu
I love you big sis
oh shut up that kid is in the way like big time
hey big sis I have a question
is it true what they say
that real love turns into stars
see mommy reads me a book and the pictures say it so
I guess the words do too
tell me sis does love really turn into stars does love really turn into stars does it does it does it
yes it does real love climbs all the way up to heaven and then turns into the stars in the night sky
a shooting star
did your book talk about what happens with shooting stars too
when they fall to earth it turns into a promise kiss
yeah right love turning into a kiss talk about a stupid fairy tale
grody growl
then promised kisses must look like stars
I bet they're all really sparkly with different kinds of colors
yeah maybe so
okay
you know what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna go get a promised kiss for you Lulu
huh
that shooting star was my love for you
I mean I love you with all of my heart
so it just has to be my love right
yay bet it's on the ground out there somewhere
that was the fateful moment
princess Lulu thought of a way out of her pesky situation
she knew how to get rid of her little brother
desire
hey moon
do you honestly love your big sister Lulu
yep I do
so can you give me a big old kiss
I will as long as you bring me a promised kiss
think you can do that
mm
all right better get in here
okay
die die die
desire growl
now I can finally be the favorite one again
without Milne the world is surely going to start wanting me once more
but just then
I'm back sis I'm back home
huh
Prince Milne who she assumed was dead came back
and what's more
here
I got your promised kiss
look how sparkly
and it's the same color as a star too
huh
this isn't a promised kiss
it's just boring old honey
come on give me a kiss
you promised you would
don't you remember
kiss me kiss me
please
you promised
come on sis
kiss me
shut up
princess Lulu threw the promised kiss that Prince Milne had brought for her
far far away
she got rid of it because it wasn't what she had wanted at all
she wasn't one to give up though
hey Milne
do you honestly love your big sister
yep I do I love you so can you please give me a big kiss
I will as long as you bring me a promised kiss think you can do that
mm
all right better get in here
okay
hey
I'm getting my desire this time there's no way I won't
I'm back sis
you promised me a kiss
come on
kiss me sis
kiss me
shut up
hey Milne
yep I do
I love you
give me a kiss
die
my realest time desire
Max
you just gotta give me a kiss now
you promised
kiss me sis
surprisingly
no matter how many times she's hit him plummeting to his death
prince Milne returned to princess Lulu over and over and over again
in his hands he would have the promised kiss
a part of honey
and with a smile he would pester her for a kiss
shut up
until one day
oh I have terrible news
it's prince Milne
he's passed away
I saw the whole thing happen
it was a tragic tragic accident
an accidental death
well all right then
everything's worked out perfectly
and so once again
princess Lulu became the kingdom's favorite bear
that dream
I had it again
simmer simmer porridge
simmer simmer softly
growl growl
and for my special finishing touch
that wasn't a dream
I killed Mitzko
I killed her with my own two hands
a bear turned human
but why
how
oh you're awake
it's you
why are you here
it's Lulu remember
curry pie
growl
like cutie pie
but with curry ha
adorable right
Lulu is so clever
never mind that
how did you get into my house
the open window
well the broken window
but it's fixed
what do you want with me
I mean you basically broke into my house
and then you start cooking
why are you even here
growl
we uh
we just wanted to come see if you were okay
you haven't been to school in a long time
so we were starting to get really worried about you
why not ask miss Yurika
she knows where I am
don't know
probably because we were so worried
worried
drop the act
I'm sure you're invisible like the others by now
invisible
no not at all
we're trying to be good friends curry ha
you're my friends
mm-hmm
for you
it's a Lulu special
I call it honey porridge
it's so tasty
it'll make you all growly gooey inside
oh Sunika
here
we can each take half
okay
I think food tastes better when we're together
no Sunika is my only friend
several years had passed since Prince Mill died
and since Princess Lulu became the kingdom's favorite
she had grown into a beautiful lady
and prince after prince visited from surrounding kingdoms
however every time
Princess Lulu
won't you please give me a promise kiss
I want to share a passionate romance with you
that will burn hotter than the sun
for that is sexy
shabba-da-doo
oh my
your highness
you mustn't be taken in by playbears like him
were I to be the lucky one
who receives your precious promised kiss
I would double your kingdom's economy
no wait
I would increase it tenfold
I'm so cool
oh my
you're both silly little fools aren't you
haven't you been told what really matters in a man
it's how cute they are
a sparkle
I'll stay by your side forever
Princess Lulu
we'll be beautiful
you'll give me a promise kiss won't you
oh my
we could keep at this
but I'm sure you get the picture
authority
the attention of her people
words of love
Princess Lulu had gotten everything
she'd ever hoped to have
and it was all thanks to Prince Milne's convenient death
however even after she had all she ever thought she desired
Lulu never felt truly happy
on the contrary she felt rather
rather plagued by an awful feeling of emptiness
as though she had misplaced something deeply precious
and then one day
what is it
if it's more princes or new dresses I don't want any
Milne
I'm back home sis and look what I have
here you go I brought you a promised kiss
how far did you have to travel to find that
oh Milne
everyone thinks that you died
yeah I know
I took a super far away
and it was real real hard
but I still made it back okay
I can't take that from you
I know I'll just throw it away again
oh don't worry
I'll find as many of these as you want me to
so kiss me sis please
you promised you would
don't you remember
Milne
who are you
here
is this your little brother's
yes it is
I found it across the valley
so I came to deliver it
did you throw this away
yeah
it still belongs to you
if you forget about the thing you've lost
then you really will lose it eventually
good talk
it was a tragic tragic accident
the way prince Milne died was awful
as always
the darling little prince said he wanted to go get some honey
to bring back for his beloved sister princess Lulu
he went up to the bees nest and was stung
that's what killed him
it all happened so quickly
you promised you would
kiss me sis
kiss me
from the beginning
Lulu hated you
but also
Lulu must have loved you from the beginning as well
well that sucks
your honey porridge is good
shame to waste it
it's because Lulu made her mad
the only thing Lulu figures she did wrong
was say we were trying to be good friends
Lulu just wanted to be nice
Lulu
thanks Kinko
my love is about making sure your love is fulfilled
Lulu feels like if she can do that
if she can help you
Lulu might be able to see him again
one more time
and that's why
why Lulu
well I have some place to be so see ya
wait
where are you going
beyond the wall of severance
to the human world
but if you do that
you're for sure gonna get killed
oh no I'll be fine
that's because I got love from her
you got love
yeah
so I'm gonna go returning
I'll see her and deliver my love
I made her a promise
we would meet again
and I would kiss her
kiss her
yes
it's a promise kiss
cute promise
kiss me sis
kiss me
so this girl is on the other side of the wall
yeah
I know she's waiting for me
but she's human right
if you meet her
she might try to kill you
yes I know
that doesn't bother you
no way
because I am a criminal bear
I refuse to back down on my love
take me with you
what
take me with you across the wall
oh please let me go along
if you take me
I can help you
we can work side by side
get you that promised kiss
why would you do that
because like you
I'm a criminal bear
you're me
before I lost mine
no that's wrong
I think you've already lost yours once
but if there's someone out there
still alive for you to meet
we'll go
even if that girl is across the wall
defendant bear Lulu Yurigasaki
I ask you this
will you give up on love
or
will you give up on kisses
I'll never give up on love
so I'll give up on kisses
growl
please oh please make me a human girl
I've just got to go to the other side of the wall
I can't let Ginko go alone
first I need you to understand
that if you make this choice
you will lose all kisses forever
they're already lost
and I'll never see them again
but not for Ginko
I know she'll still be able to see hers
so since I can't have mine
I'll help complete her promise kiss
in other words
you're entrusting Ginko Yurishiro
with the wish you failed to fulfill yourself
trying to achieve self-actualization that way
is mere self-satisfaction
it is pride
and that dear is a crime
great
I'm okay with it since I'm a criminal bear
I see
I shall now declare the verdict
Yuri
approved
proud
we go
and thus princess Lulu
correction
and thus Lulu Yurigasaki
set out with Ginko Yurishiro
as human girls
to cross the wall of severance
now
the question remains
will the promised kiss
come to pass
for that is sexy
shabba-da-doom
hmm
you